{"_id":1.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Inside which HTML element do we put JavaScript?","quiz_options":["\u003cscripting\u003e","\u003cscript\u003e","\u003cjs\u003e","\u003cjavascript\u003e"],"quiz_answer":"\u003cscript\u003e"}
{"_id":2.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Static binding uses which information for binding?","quiz_options":["type","object","both of the above","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"type"}
{"_id":3.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"What does PHP stand for?","quiz_options":["Private Home Page","Personel Hypertext Processor","PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor"}
{"_id":4.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Where is the correct place to insert JavaScript?","quiz_options":["Both the \u003chead\u003e section and \u003cbody\u003e section","\u003chead\u003e section","\u003cbody\u003e section","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"Both the \u003chead\u003e section and \u003cbody\u003e section"}
{"_id":5.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"What is correct syntax for referring to an external script called xxx.js ?","quiz_options":["\u003cscript href = \"xxx.js\"\u003e","\u003cscript src = \"xxx.js\"\u003e","\u003cscript name = \"xxx.js\"\u003e","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"\u003cscript src = \"xxx.js\"\u003e"}
{"_id":6.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"How do we create function in JvaScript?","quiz_options":["function myFunction()","function = myFunction()","function : myFunction()","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"function myFunction()"}
{"_id":7.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"How do we call function named myFunction() ?","quiz_options":["call function myFunction()","call myFunction()","myFunction()","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"myFunction()"}
{"_id":8.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"How to write if statement in JavaScript?","quiz_options":["if i=5 then","if i==5 then","if i=5","if(i==5)"],"quiz_answer":"if(i==5)"}
{"_id":9.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in a small font, as if it were in a \u003csmall\u003e tag?","quiz_options":["link()","small()","sup()","sub()"],"quiz_answer":"small()"}
{"_id":10.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Which built-in method returns the string representation of the numbers value?","quiz_options":["toValue()","toNumber()","toString()","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"toString()"}
{"_id":11.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Which of the following function of String object is used to match a regular expression against a string?","quiz_options":["concat()","match()","search()","replace()"],"quiz_answer":"match()"}
{"_id":12.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case while respecting the current locale?","quiz_options":["toLocaleLowerCase()","toLowerCase()","toString()","substring()"],"quiz_answer":"toLocaleLowerCase()"}
{"_id":13.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"What is printed in the console var foo = function foo() { console.log(foo === foo); }; foo(); ?","quiz_options":["true","false"],"quiz_answer":"true"}
{"_id":14.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"(true + false) \u003e 2 + true; What is the result?","quiz_options":["true","false","type error","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"false"}
{"_id":15.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"What are variables used in JavaScript programs?","quiz_options":["storing numbers, dates or other values","varying randomly","causing high school algebra flashbacks","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":"storing numbers, dates or other values"}
{"_id":16.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"____ JavaScript statements embedded in a HTML page can respond to user events such as mouseclicks, form input and page navigation.","quiz_options":["client-side","server-side","local","native"],"quiz_answer":"server-side()"}
{"_id":17.0,"quiz_subject":"JS","quiz_question":"Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?","quiz_options":["JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java","JavaScripts syntax is loosely based on Javas","They both originated on the island of Java","none of the above"],"quiz_answer":" JavaScripts syntax is loosely based on Javas"}
{"_id":18.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which one of these lists contains only /java programming language keywords?","quiz_options":["class, if, void, long, Int, continue","goto, instanceof, native, finally, default, throws","try, virtual, throw, final, volatile, transient","strictfp, constant, super, implements, do"],"quiz_answer":"goto, instanceof, native, finally, default, throws"}
{"_id":19.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which is the valid keyword in Java ?","quiz_options":["interface","string","Float","unsigned"],"quiz_answer":"interface"}
{"_id":20.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which one of the following will declare an array and initialize it with five numbers?","quiz_options":["Array a = new Array(5);","int [] a = {23,22,21,20,19};","int a [] = new int[5];","int [5] array;"],"quiz_answer":"int [] a = {23,22,21,20,19};"}
{"_id":21.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which cannot directly cause a thread to stop executing?","quiz_options":["Calling the SetPriority() method on a Thread object.","Calling the wait() method on an object.","Calling notify() method on an object.","Calling read() method on an InputStream object."],"quiz_answer":"Calling notify() method on an object."}
{"_id":22.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"What is the name of the method used to start a thread execution?","quiz_options":["init();","start();","run();","resume();"],"quiz_answer":"start()"}
{"_id":23.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which of the following will directly stop the execution of a Thread?","quiz_options":["wait()","notify()","notifyall()","exits synchronized code"],"quiz_answer":"wait()"}
{"_id":24.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which method must be defined by a class implementing the java.lang.Runnable interface?","quiz_options":["void run()","public void run()","public void start()","void run(int priority)"],"quiz_answer":"public void run()"}
{"_id":25.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which class does not override the equals() and hashCode() methods, inheriting them directly from class Object?","quiz_options":["java.lang.String","java.lang.Double","java.lang.StringBuffer","java.lang.Character"],"quiz_answer":"java.lang.StringBuffer"}
{"_id":26.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Assume the following method is properly synchronized and called from a thread A on an object B: wait(2000);  After calling this method, when will the thread A become a candidate to get another turn at the CPU?","quiz_options":["After thread A is notified, or after two seconds.","After the lock on B is released, or after two seconds.","Two seconds after thread A is notified.","Two seconds after lock B is released."],"quiz_answer":"After thread A is notified, or after two seconds."}
{"_id":27.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which interface does java.util.Hashtable implement?","quiz_options":["Java.util.Map","Java.util.List","Java.util.HashTable","Java.util.Collection"],"quiz_answer":"Java.util.Map"}
{"_id":28.0,"quiz_subject":"Java","quiz_question":"Which of these will create and start this thread?","quiz_options":["new Runnable(MyRunnable).start();","new Thread(MyRunnable).run();","new Thread(new MyRunnable()).start();","new MyRunnable().start();"],"quiz_answer":"new Thread(new MyRunnable()).start();"}
{"_id":29.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"The practice of separating the user from the true inner workings of an application through well-known interfaces is known as _________","quiz_options":["Polymorphism","Inheritance","Encapsulation","Abstraction"],"quiz_answer":"Encapsulation"}
{"_id":30.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which of the following term originates from the Greek language that means “having multiple forms,” defines OOP’s ability to redefine, a class’s characteristics?","quiz_options":["Abstraction","Polymorphism","Inheritance","Differential"],"quiz_answer":"Polymorphism"}
{"_id":31.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"The practice of creating objects based on predefined classes is often referred to as..","quiz_options":["class creation","object creation"," object instantiation","class instantiation"],"quiz_answer":"class instantiation"}
{"_id":32.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which one of the following property scopes is not supported by PHP?","quiz_options":["friendly","final","public","static"],"quiz_answer":"friendly"}
{"_id":33.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which one of the following can be used to instantiate an object in PHP assuming class name to be Foo?","quiz_options":["$obj = new $foo;","$obj = new foo;","$obj = new foo ();","obj = new foo ();"],"quiz_answer":"$obj = new foo ();"}
{"_id":34.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which one of the following is the right way to define a constant?","quiz_options":["constant PI = “3.1415”;","const $PI = “3.1415”;","  constant PI = ‘3.1415’;","const PI = ‘3.1415’;"],"quiz_answer":"const PI = ‘3.1415’;"}
{"_id":35.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which one of the following is the right way to call a class constant, given that the class is mathFunction?","quiz_options":["echo PI;","echo mathFunction-\u003ePI;","echo mathFunction::PI;","echo mathFunction=PI;"],"quiz_answer":"echo mathFunction::PI;"}
{"_id":36.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which one of the following is the right way to invoke a method?","quiz_options":["$object-\u003emethodName();","object-\u003emethodName();","object::methodName();","$object::methodName();"],"quiz_answer":"$object-\u003emethodName();"}
{"_id":37.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which of the following is/are the right way to declare a method? i) function functionName() { function body } ii) scope function functionName() { function body } iii) method methodName() { method body } iv) scope method methodName() { method body }","quiz_options":["Only ii)","Only iv)","i) and ii)"," iii) and iv)"],"quiz_answer":"i) and ii)"}
{"_id":38.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which of the below symbols is a newline character?","quiz_options":["\r","\n","/n","/r"],"quiz_answer":"/n"}
{"_id":39.0,"quiz_subject":"PHP","quiz_question":"Which of the below statements is equivalent to $add += $add ?","quiz_options":["$add = $add","$add = $add +$add","$add = $add + 1"," $add = $add + $add + 1"],"quiz_answer":"$add = $add +$add"}
